<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial on mgorbatyuk.dev</title>
    <link>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/tags/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorial on mgorbatyuk.dev</description>
    <image>
      <title>mgorbatyuk.dev</title>
      <url>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/images/avatar.png</url>
      <link>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/images/avatar.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.156.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mgorbatyuk.dev/tags/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to increase nuget package version automatically with Github Actions</title>
      <link>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/blog/development/2023-02-03-auto-nuget-version-increase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/blog/development/2023-02-03-auto-nuget-version-increase/</guid>
      <description>When you push new nugets to nuget.org, you need to increase the version of the package. This article describes how to do it automatically with Github Actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to integrate Identity Server into your web application</title>
      <link>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/blog/development/2021-12-26-how-to-integrate-identity-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/blog/development/2021-12-26-how-to-integrate-identity-server/</guid>
      <description>There is a tutorial how to integrate and use IdentityServer4 in your web application</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A little life hack when you work with Azure Service Bus and ASP.NET Core</title>
      <link>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/blog/development/2021-03-07-asp-net-azure-sb-queues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/blog/development/2021-03-07-asp-net-azure-sb-queues/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you work with Azure infrastructure and have to integrate message queues. It sounds quite simple: just create Azure Resource, write some code and then be happy! But what would you say if the resources are limited? What will you do if there are several teammates in your team, and all of you have to debug queues at the same time?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, I know a minor life hack for my teams. I create an InMemory Message queue engine for local development and use Azure Service Bus (or any other external MQ engine) only for remote environments. This solution allows me to not think about paid resources or concurrency access to the single development queue.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to accept and return snake case formatted JSON in ASP Web API</title>
      <link>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/blog/development/2021-02-20-snake-case-and-asp-net-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mgorbatyuk.dev/blog/development/2021-02-20-snake-case-and-asp-net-core/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The standard way to accept and return data in ASP.NET world is camel case. But at the current project, I was asked to change my ASP Web API application data processing format. I had to move all the JSON data format from &lt;code&gt;camelCase&lt;/code&gt; to &lt;code&gt;snake_case&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://mgorbatyuk.dev/images/blog/development/2021-02-20-snake-case-and-asp-net-core/snake_vs_camel.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Camel case vs Snake case&#34;  /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason for it was fact that we had to start developing React application as a SPA of our system. I thought that nothing will be a trouble, but I had met some issues. Now, I want to share with you my solution of how to make your ASP Web API and JSON in the Snake Case be the best friends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
